# Diana Savchuk

dianasav15sa@gmail.com

+447500565671

linkedin.com/in/diana-savchuk-97143923a

## Summary

Since August of this year, I have started my journey as a Web developer at the CodeYourFuture company, where I will learn HTML/CSS, Javascript, React, Express and Postgresql.

Given my previous experience in management, I have good organizational, time management, and people management skills.

## **Experience**



CodeYourFuture

Aug 2022 - Present (1 month +)

## (Clobal Restaurant Shift Manager

Global Restaurant Group Apr 2018 - Mar 2020 (2 years)

## (Clobal Restaurant Deputy Director

Global Restaurant Group

Mar 2020 - Feb 2022 (2 years)

Supervised the work of all structural divisions of the restaurant.

Organized the current organizational and executive work of the entire restaurant.

Ensured the company's fulfillment of all obligations to suppliers, customers, and creditors, including bank institutions and economic and labor contracts.

Approves the staff schedule of the restaurant, and sets salaries and allowances quarterly or as needed.

Through my work in customer service, I developed a strong ability to work under pressure as well as engage effectively in customer relations and communication.

### Education



## National University of Life and Environmental Sciences of Ukraine

Master's degree, Automation Engineer Technology/Technician Sep 2021 - Jun 2023

Program Subject Area "Automation and computer-integrated technologies"

## National University of Life and Environmental Sciences of Ukraine

Bachelor's degree. Automation and instrumentation 2017 - 2021

Program Subject Area "Automation and computer-integrated technologies"

## Skills

Communication • Research • Engineering • Analytical Skills • Leadership • Time Management